<resources>
  <string name="app_name">WatchErth</string>
  <string name="title_activity_dashboard">Dashboard</string>

  <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
  <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

  <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

  <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

  <string name="facebook_app_id">395097437693733</string>
  <string name="fb_login_protocol_scheme">fb395097437693733</string>

  <!-- resources for distance spinner in notification settings -->
  <string-array name="subscription_setting_distance">
    <item>1.0</item>
    <item>2.0</item>
    <item>3.0</item>
    <item>4.0</item>
  </string-array>

  <string name="label_sos">SEND S.O.S. SIGNAL</string>
  <string name="label_alert_sent">ALERT SENT</string>
  <string name="label_alert_instruction">Press the button for 3 seconds to send an alert message</string>
  <string name="label_alert_notification">Keep Calm! Getting in touch with you</string>

  <string name="earthquakedo">Take cover under a strong table or any other piece of furniture and stay put until the shaking stops. Search for a corner in your house.
        Stay away from glass, window doors, walls and any other weak structure that may fall.
        Try to keep your cool and don\'t run around here and there, coming out of your houses. Move away from tall buildings, trees, streetlights and utility wires.
        Once out of your houses, stay in open space till the shaking stops. Most casualties result from collapsing walls and falling objects.
        Proceed cautiously once the earthquake has stopped</string>
  <string name="cyclonedo">Check houses, secure loose tiles by cementing wherever necessary, repair doors and windows.
        Check the area around the house. Remove dead or dying trees, anchor removable objects like lumber piles, loose bricks, garbage cans, sign-boards, loose zinc sheets etc.
        Keep some wooden boards ready so that glass windows can be boarded.
        If you do not have wooden boards handy, paste paper strips on glasses to prevent splinters flying into the house.
        Keep a hurricane Lantern filled with kerosene, flash light and enough dry cells and keep them handy.</string>
  <string name="flooddo">Switch off electrical and gas appliances, and turn off services off at the mains.
        Carry your emergency kit and let your friends and family know where you are going.
        Avoid contact with flood water it may be contaminated with sewage,oil,chemicals or other substances.
        If you have to walk in standing water, use a pole or stick to ensure that you do not step into deep water, open manholes or ditches.
        Stay away from power lines electrical current can travel through water, Report power lines that are down to the power company.</string>
  <string name="volcanodo">Avoid all low-lying places because lava flows and mudflows are more likely to pass here.
    Store as much food, water, light sources and batteries that are very useful in case of emergency.
    Volcanic eruptions have ash falls so be prepared for masks or anything to cover nose and mouth.
    Seek cover in case of ash falls rock falls.</string>
  <string name="landslidedo">Prepare tour to hilly region according to information given by weather department or news channel.
    Move away from landslide path or downstream valleys quickly without wasting time.
    Keep drains clean,
    Inspect drains for - litter, leaves, plastic bags, rubble etc.
    Keep the weep holes open.</string>
  <string name="earthquakedon">Do not light a match.
        Do not move about or kick up dust.
        Stop as quickly as safety permits and stay in the vehicle. Avoid stopping near or under buildings, trees, overpasses, and utility wires</string>
  <string name="cyclonedon"> Avoid being misled by rumours.
        Don’t leave shelters until informed by the rescue personals.
        Don’t leave the safer place during lull, however minor repairs can be carried out.
        Don’t touch the loose and dangling wire from lamp post, it may have electric current.</string>
  <string name="flooddon">Don\'t walk through flowing water - currents can be deceptive, and shallow, fast moving water can knock you off your feet.
    Don\'t swim through fast flowing water - you may get swept away or struck by an object in the water.
    Don\'t drive through a flooded area - You may not be able to see abrupt drop - offs and only half a meter of flood water can carry a car away. Driving through flood water can also cause additional damage to nearby property.
    Don\'t eat any food that has come into contact with flood water.
    Don\'t reconnect your power supply until a qualified engineer has checked it. Be alert for gas leaks - do not smoke or use candles, lanterns, or open flames.</string>
  <string name="volcanodon">Don\'t go outside unless you have proper protective gear.
    Avoid low lying areas.
    Don\'t watch a volcanic eruption as it can be deadly.</string>
  <string name="landslidedon">Try to avoid construction and staying in vulnerable areas.
    Do not panic and loose energy by crying.
    Do not touch or walk over loose material and electrical wiring or pole.
    Do not built houses near steep slopes and near drainage path.
    Do not drink contaminated water directly from rivers, springs, wells but rain water if collected directly without is fine.</string>
  <string name="usa_emergency_contact">tel:1-800-985-5990</string>
  <string name="India_emergency_contact">tel:108</string>
  <string name="mexico_emergency_contact">tel:1-800-985-5990</string>
  <string name="china_emergency_contact">tel:1-240-276-2130</string>




</resources>
